https://www.worldofenvelopes.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

This website requires cookies to provide all of its features. By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies - Learn more - Hide this message
Due to the high volumes of orders we are receiving at this time, we are estimating a 7 day delay on picking and packing some of your items.
We apologise for the inconvenience and thank you for your patience.
Quick Search
Standard SizeA4C3C4C5C5+C5minusC6C7DLDL+DLminusNoSquare
Size330x1304x216450x189x183113x113215x215625x1305x315166x118250x250216x154163x12571x71250x220210x80330x21085x7560x90290x250280x20589x89450x297100x76108x92117x89119x114122x100125x120152x216155x150165x160168x164172x126183x95205x205215x85216x155225x225235x180236x230238x173300x190300x430305x225305x305310x140315x120330x236334x234345x165410x260460x32090x6538x2140x4045x4055x5557x5760x6062x9462x9863x3864x3464x3864x4764x7265x4065x6065x9468x6870x10070x14075x5575x6080x21580x8081x11382x11385x8085x8585x9088x8889x15290x7090x8592x6892x9293x13094x14395x12295x6097x4298x22898x6799x14399x3499x3899x5799x6799x6899x93100x100100x45100x50100x65100x70100x80102x108102x146102x216102x76105x105108x102108x108108x159110x76110x110110x220111x157113x81113x87114x162114x229114x235115x115115x225115x85115x90116x116120x120120x165120x200120x310120x65121x171121x184121x235124x89125x102125x125125x175126x126127x127127x190130x130130x135130x150130x180130x80130x90132x95133x184133x197135x138135x184135x197139x99140x100140x140140x145140x200140x220140x88143x203145x105145x140145x145145x90146x146147x125147x126150x150150x85152x102155x125155x155155x160155x220158x245159x210160x120160x160160x163160x230161x66162x114162x119162x210162x229162x235162x238162x80162x88164x164164x180165x100165x115165x140165x165165x65165x85165x95170x125170x127170x170170x175172x116175x110175x129175x160175x175175x305176x250180x100180x127180x140180x164180x165180x180180x230180x235180x95185x125185x138185x185190x123190x125190x127190x140190x190190x60190x75192x155194x292195x136195x139195x145195x195199x289200x144200x200200x280200x289200x95205x152210x130210x190210x65215x117215x120215x150215x83217x155220x110220x115220x215220x220220x225220x280220x40220x60220x85220x95222x122225x70226x129226x134229x105229x114229x135229x162229x324230x115230x120230x150230x162230x165230x167230x230230x95232x155234x334235x162235x205235x315235x52238x163239x164240x170240x185240x240240x340240x75241x178245x170245x205248x330248x345249x249249x352249x359250x176250x180250x320250x90251x165254x178255x345255x85260x155260x210260x260265x180265x210265x220266x186266x353267x216268x185270x185270x190270x216270x270273x222275x205278x400280x165280x180280x190280x195280x280297x210300x200300x300302x215303x213305x127305x150305x152305x230305x250305x254310x125310x220310x240310x310312x220315x165318x267320x230320x420320x450321x467324x229324x230324x240324x254325x230325x234325x250328x458330x230330x248330x250330x254330x260330x273330x279334x457335x240340x220340x235340x240340x250340x340343x195343x225345x230345x245345x260350x250350x280350x350352x249352x250353x250355x255360x250360x270360x290370x180370x285370x340380x295380x50381x125381x245381x250381x254385x285390x305394x305394x318400x280400x300405x305406x305406x318410x410415x355420x320430x320440x170444x368444x625445x300445x310445x340449x349450x320450x324457x324457x330458x295460x330460x335460x355465x368467x321470x350480x195483x330483x341495x340500x340508x381520x420525x450530x130545x180570x520595x430630x500661x442680x444
Window / PlainLeft hand sidePlainRight hand sideRound WindowWindowWindow with different size and position W1Window with different size and position W2Window with different size and position W3
SealDraw StringGrip sealGummedMagnetOpen TopPeel & SealPopperSelf sealSleeveStopperString and WasherSuper sealTuck FlapUngummed (no seal)
Primary ColourWhiteCreamManillaBrownBlackSilverGoldClearYellowOrangeRedGreenBluePurplePinkGrey
Material20%+ BambooAdhesive LabelCardCard and PolyethyleneClear PolyethyleneCorrugated CardboardEnduroEucalyptus PaperF FluteFoilKraftKraft BoardKraft Paper, Bubble FilmLined boardOPPOriented PolypropylenePaperPaper / CardPaper and BoardPolyPolyester FibrePolyethylenePolyethylene, Foil and PaperPP5 PolypropyleneRecycled PaperTranslucent PaperTranslucent pH7 PaperTranslucent PolyethyleneTyvekWhite Lined Board
Material weight 100 Gsm100 Microns110 Gsm115 Gsm120 Gsm125 Gsm127 Gsm130 Gsm135 Gsm140 Gsm145 Gsm150 Gsm155 Gsm160 Gsm165 Gsm170 Gsm175 Gsm180 Gsm190 Gsm2 Gsm200 Gsm22 Gsm225 Gsm2260 Gsm230 Gsm240 Gsm250 Gsm260 Gsm270 Gsm28 Gsm280 Gsm30 Gsm30 Microns300 Gsm340 Gsm35 Microns350 Gsm37 Gsm37 Microns40 Gsm40 Microns400 Gsm420 Gsm50 Gsm50 Microns500 Gsm55 Gsm59 Gsm60 Microns68 Gsm70 Gsm70 Microns75 Gsm80 Gsm81 Gsm90 Gsm92 Gsm
Search Clear All
Privacy and Cookie Policy
1. Introduction
1.1 We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of www.worldofenvelopes.com; in this policy we explain how we will handle your personal data.
1.2 We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website.
1.3 Our website incorporates privacy controls which affect how we will process your personal data. By using the privacy controls, you can specify whether you would like to receive direct marketing communications. You can access the privacy controls via https://www.worldofenvelopes.com/returns-policy.
2. How we use your personal data
2.1 In this Section 2 we have set out:
(a) the general categories of personal data that we may process;
(b) the purposes for which we may process personal data; and
(c) the legal bases of the processing.
2.2 We may process data about your use of our website and services ("usage data"). The usage data may include your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, as well as information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of the usage data is our analytics tracking system. This usage data may be processed for the purposes of analysing the use of the website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely monitoring and improving our website and services.
2.3 We may process your account data ("account data"). The account data may include your name and email address. The source of the account data is you. The account data may be processed for the purposes of providing our services, and communicating with you. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
2.4 We may process information that you post for publication on our website or through our services ("publication data"). The publication data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract.
2.5 We may process information contained in any enquiry you submit to us regarding goods and services ("enquiry data"). The enquiry data may be processed for the purposes of offering, marketing and selling relevant goods and/or services to you. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
2.6 We may process information relating to transactions, including purchases of goods and services, that you enter into with us and/or through our website ("transaction data"). The transaction data may include your contact details, your card details and the transaction details. The transaction data may be processed for the purpose of supplying the purchased goods and services and keeping proper records of those transactions. The legal basis for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps, at your request, to enter into such a contract and our legitimate interests, namely our interest in the proper administration of our website and business.
2.7 We may process information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and newsletters ("notification data"). The notification data may be processed for the purposes of sending you the relevant notifications and newsletters. The legal basis for this processing is consent.
2.8 We may process information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us ("correspondence data"). The correspondence data may include the communication content and metadata associated with the communication. Our website will generate the metadata associated with communications made using the website contact forms. The correspondence data may be processed for the purposes of communicating with you and record-keeping. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper administration of our website and business and communications with users.
2.9 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others.
2.10 We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.
2.11 In addition to the specific purposes for which we may process your personal data set out in this Section 2, we may also process any of your personal data where such processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
3. Providing your personal data to others
3.1 We may disclose your personal data to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and on the legal bases, set out in this policy.
3.2 We may disclose your personal data to our insurers and/or professional advisers insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, obtaining professional advice, or the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure
3.3 Financial transactions relating to our website and services are handled by our payment services providers. We will share transaction data with our payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.
3.4 In addition to the specific disclosures of personal data set out in this Section 3, we may disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person. We may also disclose your personal data where such disclosure is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure.
4. International transfers of your personal data
4.1 In this Section 4, we provide information about the circumstances in which your personal data may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA).
4.2 You acknowledge that personal data that you submit for publication through our website or services may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.
5. Retaining and deleting personal data
5.1 This Section 5 sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal data.
5.2 Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.
5.3 Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section 5, we may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
6. Amendments
6.1 We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website.
6.2 You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy.
6.3 We may notify you of changes to this policy by email.
7. Your rights
7.1 In this Section 7, we have summarised the rights that you have under data protection law. Some of the rights are complex, and not all of the details have been included in our summaries. Accordingly, you should read the relevant laws and guidance from the regulatory authorities for a full explanation of these rights.
7.2 Your principal rights under data protection law are:
(a) the right to access;
(b) the right to rectification;
(c) the right to erasure;
(d) the right to restrict processing;
(e) the right to object to processing;
(f) the right to data portability;
(g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and
(h) the right to withdraw consent.
7.3 You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information. That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee. You can access your personal data by visiting my account details when logged into our website.
7.4 You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.
7.5 In some circumstances you have the right to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay. Those circumstances include: the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed. However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure. The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; for compliance with a legal obligation; or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
7.6 In some circumstances you have the right to restrict the processing of your personal data. Those circumstances are: you contest the accuracy of the personal data; processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; and you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection. Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data. However, we will only otherwise process it: with your consent; for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims; for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or for reasons of important public interest.
7.7 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal information unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
7.8 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.
7.9 You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.
7.10 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:
(a) consent; or
(b) that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract,
and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.
7.11 If you consider that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.
7.12 To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal information is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.
7.13 You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us, in addition to the other methods specified in this Section 7.
8. Personal data of children
8.1 If we have reason to believe that we hold personal data of a person under that age in our databases, we will delete that personal data.
9. Updating information
9.1 Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
10. About cookies
10.1 A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
10.2 Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
10.3 Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.
11. Cookies that we use
11.1 We use cookies for the following purposes:
(a) authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website;
(b) status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website;
(c) shopping cart - we use cookies to maintain the state of your shopping cart as you navigate our website;
(d) personalisation - we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalise our website for you;
(e) security - we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials, and to protect our website and services generally;
(f) advertising - we use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to you;
(g) analysis - we use cookies to help us to analyse the use and performance of our website and services; and
(h) cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally.
12. Cookies used by our service providers
12.1 Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.
12.2 We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy
13. Managing cookies
13.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:
(a) https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);
(b) https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox);
(c) http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);
(d) https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);
(e) https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and
(f) https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge).
13.2 Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
13.3 If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.
14. Our details
14.1 This website is owned and operated by Envelopes Ltd.
14.3 Our principal place of business is at Envelopes Ltd. First Floor, Unit B, Knaves Beech Way, Loudwater, Bucks HP10 9QY. United Kingdom.
14.4 You can contact us:
(a) by post, to the postal address given above;
(b) using our website contact form;
(c) by telephone, on the contact number published on our website or
(d) by email, using the email address published on our website.
Copyright © 2019 Envelopes Ltd Design & Developed by StreamMarket
